Hello guys, good morning, I hope you are doing
well. In this video, I want to
teach you how to bypass the national network
and easily go to YouTube and
watch its videos. For this, we
need two files, the links to which I have included in the caption
.  If for any reason you couldn't download it, it
's on our Telegram channel.
First of all, these files are zipped and we need to
unzip them.  Right-
click and select the Extract A option.
This is the same and this part is the
address that is the file itself and next to
your file this is the zipped file this is
actually where this file is that
came from
so these are the files that were extracted
actually from the zipped file
we have a file inside this file
in the xconfig folder
that we need to copy this to
create the certificate we copy this with control
c or we can also copy from this part
and paste it into the vita file
with control v and sometimes you can
click this option
this option click ram it will be pasted it will be pasted with control v
then what does the
certificate generator do it it will create
a personal certificate for you and be sure to be
careful and pay attention to this point
that you should not take someone else's certificate
or give your certificate to
someone else
twice when you click on it this will run press
any button on your keyboard
you want to press and this will come
out and d files i.e. d certificates will be
created for you these d  Now
automatically when I run the certificate generator,
this two files were automatically
added to this folder and you double-
click on the MySert file, you run it
and click on the Install Local Certificate Next button.
Then you select this section.
This section, when you select it, will
be activated for you. When
you click on the browser, it will show you a few options
that you have to click on the second option.
Click Next. Finish. And
when this message says full success, it means that it
was successful and you have done very well so far.
Then it will come in. Now I'm behind, maybe you're
confused. Inside this same .exe file, you
run this .exe file.
Double-click on it and it will run.
When it opens, you
can write a name for it,
anything you want. Then
you select the address for the address and let me
tell you where to go. The same file that I
told you is config. And this is it.  We
unzipped it and inside the X-ray
config there is something with the extension json.
You select this and click open. When
you click open, this is what it will
enter and you will type the code on the X-
ray. You will
read this part and config.
When you click this, a config will
be added for you here so that you can turn on your filter breaker
or leave it on this config.
You will set this to select mode. When
you set this to select mode, it will turn completely blue.
Then you right-click and click Set from Active.
Then
after you click Set from Active, you will come to this
section. Click here. You will
see the Vtory file here.
Right-click. A few options will come to you. You
have to select the proxy system.
When you select this,
your configuration is now working. When this
turns red, it means that your
filter breaker is active and is now patched. For example,
let's go to YouTube and see if it opens or
you can safely watch
YouTube videos now and
the speed is very good.
Good luck.  God-fearing